[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is NOT a species of rhinoceros?", "correct_answer": "African Rhino", "incorrect_answers": ["Indian Rhino", "Javan Rhino", "Sumatran Rhino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor sued a Los Angeles magazine for publishing a computer-generated image of him wearing a dress?", "correct_answer": "Dustin Hoffman", "incorrect_answers": ["Al Pacino", "Patrick Swayze", "Weslery Snipes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Light, just as wind, has the ability to push objects in its path.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This food was invented in 1890 by a doctor, for his patients with decayed teeth. Before the 1960s it was hardly consumed outside America, as the rest of the world did not relish it.", "correct_answer": "Peanut butter", "incorrect_answers": ["Butter", "Olive oil", "Cream"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To which of these countries is the pistachio tree native?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Turkey", "Turkmenistan", "Iran"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the rabbit in Disneys animated movie Bambi?", "correct_answer": "Thumper", "incorrect_answers": ["Flower", "Faline", "Ronno"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In his Theory of Relativity, Albert Einstein discloses that when you multiply the speed of light by the mass you get what?", "correct_answer": "The energy", "incorrect_answers": ["The density", "The volume", "The frequency"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Loch Ness is the largest body of water in which huge geologic fault?", "correct_answer": "Great Glen", "incorrect_answers": ["Scotia", "Augustus", "Highlands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many individual muscles are in an elephants trunk?", "correct_answer": "40,000", "incorrect_answers": ["2,000", "10,000", "500"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the US, all Medicare Part B participants pay a monthly premium for the service.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do the following classic movies have in common: Spartacus, Rosemarys Baby, The Magnificent Seven, and The Ten Commandments?", "correct_answer": "None of them made it to the Top 100 list.", "incorrect_answers": ["They were all written by Ed Wood.", "They were all made for under five million dollars.", "They were all made in the 1960s."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Typically, how many random items can human short-term memory store?", "correct_answer": "6-8", "incorrect_answers": ["3-4", "9-11", "15-17"]}]